magnify.net 2017-10-22

# Privacy | Waywire Enterprise – The Video Curation Platform For Brands and Publishers

Privacy Policy

We at Waywire Global, Inc. (“WayWire,” “we,” “us,” “our”) know that our users (“you,” “your”) care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the Website or Services in any manner, or downloading the application, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. Capitalized terms used herein that are not defined shall have the meaning given to them in the WayWire Terms of Use.

I. WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or the Services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.  
We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined in our Terms of Use). If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at abuse@waywireglobal.com

II. WHAT INFORMATION DOES WAYWIRE COLLECT?

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this Personal Information to personalize and improve our services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how users utilize the Services, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties (described in this Section and in Section III below). We collect the following types of information:  
A. Information You Provide to Us:

When you register for the Services or sign in using a Third Party Website, you may provide Personal Information, such as your name, username, password, and email address, and optional information such as birthdate, location, gender, location and occupation. You acknowledge that this information is personal to you, and by creating an account on the Services, you allow others, including us, to identify you. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe from certain of these messages through the Services, but certain communications, such as important information regarding the Services are not subject to unsubscription. You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as your location or a profile picture.  
When you access the Services through a Third Party Website, such as Facebook Connect, Twitter or Google +, then we may receive additional information about you through that Third Party Website. In each case, we will collect and record the information you have provided such as your username, email address, and third-party account credentials (for example, your log-in credentials for Facebook or other third party sites). We don’t actually store your passwords for those Third Party Websites. Instead, we just use an authentication token to verify your user name. We also may be able to collect other information about you (such as picture, gender, age, education, occupation, hobbies, interests, relationship status, zip code, etc.) from Third Party Websites (in accordance with the Terms of Use of those Third Party Websites), which would then also be covered by this Privacy Policy.  
You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you cannot be individually identified, and provide that information to our partners.  
B. Information Collected Automatically:

Whenever you interact with the Services, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some features of our Services. Our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to your computer or device, when you click on ads that appear through the Services. Also, if you click on a link to a Third Party Website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.  
When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of users of the Services), we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users use parts of the Services, so that we can make the Services appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.  
C. E-mail and Other Communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may send you promotional offers on behalf of other businesses, or communicate with you about your use of the Services. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by unsubscribe@waywireglobal.com Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

III. WILL WAYWIRE SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form with third parties as described below. In the future, we may have advertising;

A. Advertisers: We allow advertisers and/or merchant partners (“Advertisers”) to choose the demographic information of users who will see their advertisements and/or promotional offers and you agree that we may provide any of the information we have collected from you in non-personally identifiable form to an Advertiser, in order for that Advertiser to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements and/or offers. For example, we might use the fact you are located in New York to show you ads or offers for New York businesses, but we will not tell such businesses who you are.] 

B. We may deliver a file to you through the Services (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

C. Affiliated Businesses and Third Party Websites We Do Not Control: In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we’re affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through the Services (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. One such service may include the ability for you to automatically transmit information from Third Party Websites to your profile on the Services or to automatically transmit information in your profile to your third party account. We have no control over the policies and practices of Third Party Websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such business’ or websites’ policies.

D. Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

E. User Profiles and Submissions: Certain user profile information, including without limitation a user’s name, location, and any video or image content that such user has uploaded to the Services may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services or address your request for WayWire’s services. Your account privacy settings allow you to limit the other users who can see the Personal Information in your user profile and/or what information in your user profile is visible to others. Any content you upload to your public user profile, along with any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by others. Your user name may also be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images or videos through the Services and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Additionally, if you sign into the Services through a third party social networking site or service, your list of “friends” from that site or service may be automatically imported to the Services, and such “friends,” if they are also registered users of the Services, may be able to access certain non-public information you have entered in your user profile. Again, we do not control the policies and practices of any other third party site or service.

F. Business Transfers: We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

G. Protection of WayWire and Others: We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of WayWire, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

H. With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties in personally identifiable form, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

IV. IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a Third Party Website, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that Third Party Website. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.  
We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.  
The Services may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site’s Privacy Policy.

V. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you’ve provided to us:  
name and password  
email address  
location  
user image  
linked accounts to Third Party Sites  
The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Services change. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at abuse@waywireglobal.com  
Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information, which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to: abuse@waywireglobal.com

VI. WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?

You can always opt not to disclose information to use, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features.  
You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained in Section V above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Please note that some information (including without limitation any User Submissions you may have posted in a manner other users can view) may remain in our records and/or on our website after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

VII. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement through the Services or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Services after such changes have been first posted.

VIII. QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to info@waywireglobal.com and we will try to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: September 29, 2017
